Reach your hands out,
cut through the wind,
and forge ahead, drawing your own map as you go!
We can't even tell left from right
in this tempest-tossed era
Even the values we've honed
seem ready to crumble
Is the compass leading us true,
or is it leading us astray?
Nobody knows for sure!
Just breathe deep, close your eyes
and you'll find your soul guiding the way!
Reach your hands out,
cut through the wind,
and kick away the darkness!
I'm doing this for myself,
and you're doing this for yourself too, right?
Forge ahead, painting the world in your own colors!
Explain yourself, Drake!
This is my brand of justice!
I envy you...
Finger Pistol.
Did you write your wish?
Light up the sky lantern boats!
Amazing! Amazing!
It's so amaziiiing!
Right, let's send them off!
Send your wishes unto the skies!
Daddy!
Gum-Gum...
...Hydra!
He's bending the direction
of his attacks?!
That's impossible!
Rubber doesn't work like that!
Owwie!
Stop it! That hurts!
That hurts!
I'm beggin ya...
...pwease stop!
Yer still drunk?!
Don't think you're the only one
that can see what's coming...
How 'bout we play copycat...
Like this?
Eeeyowowowow!
He ate me!
Lemme out, ya jackass!
Open up!
Blast Breath!
Boundman!
That son of a...!
Man, I'm all beat up!
Come back for more, huh?
How much longer can I last?
This is my last Gear 4!
I don't got any more
time to waste!
Don't quit on me, Gear 4!
Crap!
I see now...
That power of his is
surprisingly tough.
The rubber power, that is.
Shuddup!
absolutely gotta
kick your ass outta here!
Wano's people...
...can hardly find water to drink!
They can't eat 'til they're full!
That's all while you're still around!
That goes without saying!
They lost, after all.
You oughta thank me
for not murderin' the bunch!
I don't give a crap
whose side you're on...
...but Wano's people are
experienced losers!
The non-violent weak!
Those who died with dignity!
Even seen a bunch o' failures
make up excuses!
Shuddup!
The samurai are strong!
Strong, you say?
Or just acting tough?
Winners don't need
no flowery titles!
Which one are you...
Straw Hat?!
Gum-Gum...
...Over-Kong Gun!
Not yet!
I gotta make sure
he's down and out...
...while I can still use Gear 4!
Thunder Bellow...
...Bagua!
No leaving allowed, strength!
One more shot!
Let's give this the perfect ending!
If this don't work...
Show me what ya got, whelp!
...then I lose!
Gum-Gum
Over...
Thunder Bellow...
Iron Body!
Wha?!
CP-03!
Why are they here?!
Eh?
Luffy's voice...
I can no longer hear it...?
Battle of the Skull Dome Rooftop...
The victor:
Kaido the Beast King.
You know what this means
for you, I presume...?
You trash!
Kawamatsu-san!
The ceiling's about to collapse!
You must evacuate!
Thousands of our comrades
remain within the castle!
And we will make it
home together, all of us!
Alas, we are in midair!
There is no water to be had!
There is naught we can do
to extinguish this blaze!
You must all flee, I beg you!
There is no honor
in burning to death!
Blast Breath?!
It... cannot be...!
Kaido...!
Where's that boss of yours?!
Bring me Oden's son!
I wanna hear Momonosuke himself
announce surrender!
Straw Hat Luffy's dead!
Huh?
Luffy's dead?!
Straw Hatter's voice...
Vanished!
So he was no match for
an Emperor of the Sea...
What did you say...
about Luffy?
It can't be true...
There's no way...
...Luffy was killed!
If anybody else still wants to
challenge me, step right up!
I'm in the mood to
crack some more skulls.
He did it!
Kaido-sama's claimed total victory!
Big Bro Luffy...-
Don'cha go dyin' on me...!
Hey!
Don't even think about goin', nope!
You want him to
keep mouthing off?!
What the hell's that
overgrown snake on about, anyway?!
Keep those damn lies to yourself!
Luffy's dead?
Don't even think about telling me
some impossible lie!
When Luffy says he's going to win....
he'll win, no matter what!
There's no way Luffy lost!
Of course he's not dead!
That's ridiculous!
Liar!
Oh? Well, at least one of you's
got some moxie...
I don't believe you!
Since I'm such a nice guy,
I'll show ya what it means to be a loser!
Blast Breath!
Get back!
O-Nami-chan!
Don't lose your head!
Not 'til all's said and done!
Luffy...
Just as planned, Onigashima's gonna land
on the Flower Capital!
I ain't some pushover like Orochi!
He was too lenient.
This country is one giant
weapons factory!
Woman or child, I don't care who you are!
Everybody's a slave!
Exhausted from working?
Drop dead, for all I care!
That's all your lives
are worth, anyway!
Even if we lose slaves,
there's plenty more where that came from!
You dared to fight back against me,
and earned my wrath!
This is what it means to lose in war!
And the price of your defeat:
your rights as humans, and your hope!
Bring Momonosuke to me!
The fighting doesn't stop until I've dealt with him!
Wano is finished, slaves!
Your children, and your children's children
will drown in despair!
Accept these terms of defeat!
N-Not my wife and children!
Hey, now's our chance!
Lop off Kid's and Law's heads!
They're practically dead anyway!
You might've beaten Big Mom,
our last line of defense is Kaido-san!
You guys never stood a chance!
Damn nobodies...
Protect the captains!
Kaido?!
This ain't good!
We gotta save everyone!
Let's go!
Okay!
Mrrrrow!
The inferno's on all sides!
We're done for!
Is there no way out?!
Look for an exit!
I'm gonna fight, Trafalgar...
No surrender...
Ain't gonna go down quietly!
Dammit, Straw Hatter...!
Pre... Preposterous!
Impossible, I say!
What are we to do against someone
whom even Luffy could not defeat?!
We keep going until
we've breathed our last!
We must fight,
even if it means death!
Is that not what a samurai is?!
Who but us can do it now?!
Everyone else is torn to shreds!
Even Kaido must be
heavily wounded by now!
Speak not such foolishness!
After all, he is an Emperor of the Sea!
We misjudged the depths
of his strength!
We no longer have a chance!
We would only be adding more corpses to the pile!
It is time to admit defeat!
We did the best we could!
Much as it galls me,
if Luffy has indeed lost,
we must surrender!
Absolutely not!
You will do no such thing!
What meaning is there in survival...
...if we return to slavery,
counting the days until we die?!
Surrender does not mean salvation!
You absolutely will not surrender!
The regional Daimyo that
never yielded to Orochi...
...died nobly, yet much to their chagrin.
How the last twenty years of Wano are defined,
hinges upon this war we wage!
Momonosuke-kun...
If you would let it all go to waste...
...then let us face death together!
Momonosuke..
Uh?
Momonosuke!
I hear them!
How long has it been...!
Zunesha, what is it you speak of?!
I hear the Drums of Liberation!
For the first time
in eight hundred years...
He is here, I am certain!
Wh... Who is?!
Joyboy...
...has returned!